<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251" ?>
<string_table>
    <string id="ui_mm_prst_warfare_alifeoverhaul">
        <text>Alife Overhaul - Default (1x)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_prst_warfare_alifeoverhaul_faster">
        <text>Alife Overhaul - Fast (2x)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_prst_warfare_alifeoverhaul_veryfast">
        <text>Alife Overhaul - Rapid (5x)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_prst_warfare_alifeoverhaul_rapidtest">
        <text>Alife Overhaul - Test (10x)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_use_old_auto_capture">
        <text>Use old auto-capture method</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_use_old_auto_capture_desc">
        <text>When this option is enabled, autocapture will occur using the old method, where a squad is spawned on top
            of your position for free once the capture time has elapsed.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_hide_lair_smarts">
        <text>Hide lair smart terrains</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_hide_lair_smarts_desc">
        <text>When enabled, the PDA will not display icons for smart terrains with no useful properties, such as purely
            mutant lair terrains.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_actor_support_goodwill_base">
        <text>Goodwill on kill: base</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_actor_support_goodwill_base_desc">
        <text>When you kill an enemy, you will be granted this amount of goodwill with your faction plus a bonus based
            on the victim's rank and the multiplier: goodwill = base + (enemy rank * rank multiplier). Loners receive
            50% of this value.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_actor_support_goodwill_weight">
        <text>Goodwill on kill: enemy rank multiplier</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_actor_support_goodwill_weight_desc">
        <text>This setting affects the bonus amount of faction goodwill granted on kill based on the victim's rank. The
            goodwill gained is equal to: goodwill = base + (enemy rank * rank multiplier)
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_max_squads_per_level_lab">
        <text>Max monster squads per level (laboratories)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_max_squads_per_level_lab_desc">
        <text>This setting is the same as the "max monster squads per level" setting, but applies for all underground
            and laboratory levels.
        </text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_territory_diplo_penalty">
        <text>Contested terrains strain relations</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_territory_diplo_penalty_desc">
        <text>When this setting is enabled, two neutral factions contesting a single point will become upset with each
            other if one of them 'steals' the location from the other. This puts pressure on neutral factions that share
            a border. Works best with a relations addon, or lowered death_value in dynamic_faction_relations.ltx
        </text>
    </string>

    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_south">
        <text>Rare mutant % chance (Southern Zone)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_south_desc">
        <text>The percent chance that a mutant spawn in military warehouses/dead city/truck cemetery and south will be a
            rare mutant (controller, chimera, etc). Default: 3
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_north">
        <text>Rare mutant % chance (Northern Zone)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_north_desc">
        <text>The percent chance that a mutant spawn in Limansk/red forest/radar and north will be a rare mutant
            (controller, chimera, etc). Default: 10
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_lab">
        <text>Rare mutant % chance (Laboratories)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_monster_rare_chance_lab_desc">
        <text>The percent chance that a mutant spawn in a laboratory will be a rare mutant (controller, chimera, etc).
            Default: 50
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_prevent_mainbase_attacks">
        <text>Disincentivise Attacks on Main Bases</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_prevent_mainbase_attacks_desc">
        <text>When this setting is enabled, all factions will no longer attack main bases of other factions unless they
            have no other available target. For example, the Freedom Base will no longer send an attack to the Duty Base
            at the Bar until no other capturable locations exist within linked-level distance (Army Warehouses, Dead
            City, Red Forest, Truck Cemetery). Enable this setting if you want to ensure that unique NPCs don't die from
            early invasions. DISABLE this setting when using randomized starting locations!
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_offline_combat_distance">
        <text>Offline Combat Distance (Warfare ONLY)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_offline_combat_distance_desc">
        <text>Maximum distance, in meters, that offline squads will engage in offline combat when "Full" offline combat
            is used. Default: 50
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_overflow_overrides_manual_control">
        <text>Automate overflow squad handling during manual control</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_overflow_overrides_manual_control_desc">
        <text>Typically, when manual faction control is disabled, overflow squads (i.e. squads surpassing the smart
            terrain limit) are automatically re-assigned. When manual faction control is enabled, overflow squads are no
            longer handled automatically. Toggling this setting on restores the automated handling of these squads while
            preserving the rest of the manual faction control functionality.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_extra_loner_fog_of_war">
        <text>Extra fog of war for loner players</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_extra_loner_fog_of_war_desc">
        <text>When this setting is active, players playing as 'free stalkers' will not be able to see loner squads or
            outposts outside of their fog of war distance unless they use PDA v2 or PDA v3. This is similar to
            non-Warfare vision. If this setting is disabled, bases and squads of free stalkers will be visible even with
            PDA v1. This setting is only functional when fog of war is enabled.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_based_combat_multiplier">
		<text>Distance-based combat multiplier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_based_combat_multiplier_desc">
		<text>Enable distance-based combat effectiveness multipliers. Squads perform better when fighting near friendly strategic locations like bases, resources, territory, and lairs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_min_multiplier">
		<text>Distance combat min multiplier</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_min_multiplier_desc">
		<text>The minimum combat effectiveness multiplier applied when squads are far from any friendly strategic locations. This is the baseline combat strength used at maximum distance.</text>	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_base">
		<text>Distance combat max multiplier (base)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_base_desc">
		<text>Maximum combat effectiveness multiplier when near friendly bases. Bases provide the strongest strategic support and highest combat bonus.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_resource">
		<text>Distance combat max multiplier (resource)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_resource_desc">
		<text>Maximum combat effectiveness multiplier when near friendly resource points. Resources provide moderate support through supplies and equipment.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_territory">
		<text>Distance combat max multiplier (territory)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_territory_desc">
		<text>Maximum combat effectiveness multiplier when near friendly territory. Controlled territory provides basic support through familiar terrain.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_lair">
		<text>Distance combat max multiplier (lair)</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_multiplier_lair_desc">
		<text>Maximum combat effectiveness multiplier when near friendly lairs.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_distance">
		<text>Distance combat max distance</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_distance_combat_max_distance_desc">
		<text>The maximum distance at which distance-based combat multipliers are calculated. Squads beyond this distance from friendly strategic locations receive the minimum multiplier.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_use_new_resurgence_logic">
		<text>Use new resurgence logic</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_general_use_new_resurgence_logic_desc">
		<text>When enabled, uses improved emergency resurrection system for extinct factions. Creates powerful squads that target the closest enemy/empty strategic locations when a faction has zero bases. When disabled, uses the original random resurgence system.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_faction_use_bases_not_resources">
        <text>Squad quality depends on base count (instead of resources)</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_use_bases_not_resources_desc">
        <text>Normally, a faction's squad quality is calculated based on the number of resources it holds. When this
            option is selected, this faction's squad quality will be calculated based on number of held bases instead.
            Primarily meant to be used for factions that don't care about resources (ex: army).
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_offline_power_multiplier_desc">
        <text>Squad power in offline combat is multiplied by this amount. If this is set to 2, for instance, squads that
            are a part of this faction will deal twice as much damage as typical squads in offline combat.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_expansion_aggression_desc">
        <text>The overall aggression and offensive responsiveness of a faction. More aggressive factions will send
            squads to capture empty targets sooner, add additional targets to each of their bases faster, and plan
            invasions to those targets sooner. Higher aggression will also cause a faction to prioritize carrying out
            invasion plans sooner by sending squads from nearby bases, whereas less aggressive factions will be more
            content to keep their squads at their current locations.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_night_activity_chance_desc">
        <text>The chance that a faction will send out invasion forces or send patrol squads anywhere during the night
            time. Night time is considered as between the hours of 8:00pm and 6:00am, or 20:00 and 6:00. Whether a smart
            terrain can be active during nighttime is decided once per night per smart terrain. For free stalker and
            ecologist factions, this sets the likelihood for a squad to visit another resource point instead of going
            back to base for the night.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_faction_respawn_desc">
        <text>This is how many in-game minutes it takes for a faction to spawn a squad from a base point if they own
            only one base. As your faction gains more bases, each individual base will have a slightly longer spawn time
            approaching that of the maximum respawn time. The actual respawn time of a given base is linearly
            interpolated based on the min/max respawn values and the percentage of bases in the Zone you control.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_faction_respawn_desc">
        <text>This is how many in-game minutes it takes for a faction to spawn a squad from a base point if they own all
            the bases in the Zone. As your faction gains more bases, each individual base will have a slightly longer
            spawn time approaching that of the maximum respawn time. The actual respawn time of a given base is linearly
            interpolated based on the min/max respawn values and the percentage of bases in the Zone you control. For
            reference, there are roughly 80 base points in the Zone.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_invasion_size_desc">
        <text>The minimum invasion size factor. A random number between the minimum and maximum invasion size factors is
            multiplied by the calculated invasion size to give the number of squads that a base will invade with. The
            size of the invasion force is calculated using the max capacity of the target location, reinforcement
            potential of any enemy locations near the target, the relative difference in squad power between the
            factions, and these min/max factors. The invasion size cannot be more than twice the maximum capacity of the
            origin base (ex: if a base with max capacity of 2 plans to invade a target with max capacity of 5, the
            invasion can be no larger than 4 squads). If this limitation prevents a small base from planning an adequate
            invasion, that base will instead contribute squads to a larger nearby base's invasion force.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_invasion_size_desc">
        <text>The maximum invasion size factor. A random number between the minimum and maximum invasion size factors is
            multiplied by the calculated invasion size to give the number of squads that a base will invade with. The
            size of the invasion force is calculated using the max capacity of the target location, reinforcement
            potential of any enemy locations near the target, the relative difference in squad power between the
            factions, and these min/max factors. The invasion size cannot be more than twice the maximum capacity of the
            origin base (ex: if a base with max capacity of 2 plans to invade a target with max capacity of 5, the
            invasion can be no larger than 4 squads). If this limitation prevents a small base from planning an adequate
            invasion, that base will instead contribute squads to a larger nearby base's invasion force. This value is
            also used for defense to determine the desired power factor versus incoming enemy forces: a value of 1.5
            means that the defending base will try to call reinforcements to get a power advantage 1.5x that of the
            enemy invasion.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_patrol_squads_desc">
        <text>The minimum patrol squad population factor. When a faction owns no bases, each base would (theoretically
            since they don't own any) have min_patrol_squads * max_population amount of patrol squads.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_patrol_squads_desc">
        <text>The maximum patrol squad population factor. When a faction owns every base, each base will have
            max_patrol_squads * max_population amount of patrol squads.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_patrol_time_desc">
        <text>This is how many in-game minutes it takes for a faction to spawn a patrol squad from a base point if they
            own only one base. As your faction gains more bases, each individual base will have a slightly longer patrol
            spawn time approaching that of the maximum patrol respawn time. The actual patrol respawn time of a given
            base is linearly interpolated based on the min/max patrol respawn values and the percentage of bases in the
            Zone you control.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_patrol_time_desc">
        <text>This is how many in-game minutes it takes for a faction to spawn a patrol squad from a base point if they
            own every base in the Zone. As your faction gains more bases, each individual base will have a slightly
            longer patrol spawn time approaching that of the maximum patrol respawn time. The actual patrol respawn time
            of a given base is linearly interpolated based on the min/max patrol respawn values and the percentage of
            bases in the Zone you control. For reference, there are roughly 80 bases in the Zone.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_patrol_hunt_chance_desc">
        <text>When a base is looking for a new target for a patrol squad, and if there is an enemy patrol squad on the
            current level or a linked level, this is the chance that the base will assign the enemy patrol squad as a
            target; if the squad is not assigned an enemy patrol squad as a target then it will be assigned a
            territory/lair point near the base to patrol as usual.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_patrol_rest_time_desc">
        <text>The minimum amount of time a patrol squad will wait at a territory/lair point. Night activity chance will
            also affect whether or not they are sent to a new point.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_patrol_rest_time_desc">
        <text>The maximum amount of time a patrol squad will wait at a territory/lair point. Night activity chance will
            also affect whether or not they are sent to a new point.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_faction_resurgence_chance">
        <text>Resurgence Chance</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_resurgence_chance_desc">
        <text>When a faction owns zero bases, they are considered 'defeated'. Once defeated, they have a chance for a
            'resurgence', where a large attack force appears in an attempt to capture a random enemy base on the map.
            The timer for this attack depends on the minimum and maximum resurgence times. Additionally, there is a
            chance that the resurgence attempt will be skipped over: a resurgence chance of 50 will skip half of all
            resurgence attempts, while a resurgence chance of 0 will always skip attempts (as if the faction is
            permanently defeated).
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_random_squad_count_desc">
        <text>When enabled, every squad for this faction will have a random number of NPCs between
            min_random_squad_count and max_random_squad_count.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_random_squad_count_desc">
        <text>When random_squad_count is enabled, this is the minimum number of NPCs a squad will have for this
            faction.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_random_squad_count_desc">
        <text>When random_squad_count is enabled, this is the maximum number of NPCs a squad will have for this
            faction.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_random_patrols_desc">
        <text>Random patrols are squads that periodically target locations all over. They spawn preferentially on a
            faction's owned points, otherwise they can spawn anywhere in the Zone. Their targeting is influenced by your
            faction's priorities for base/resource/territory/levels. They can be temporarily commanded by you to move to
            certain points, but will eventually pick their own target after some amount of idle time.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_random_patrols_desc">
        <text>This is the absolute maximum amount of random patrols a faction can have at once.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_random_patrol_time_desc">
        <text>The lowest possible time for a new random patrol of this faction to spawn. The actual spawn time is
            randomly chosen between this number and the maximum random patrol time.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_random_patrol_time_desc">
        <text>The highest possible time for a new random patrol of this faction to spawn. The actual spawn time is
            randomly chosen between this number and the minimum random patrol time.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_invasion_departure_chance_desc">
        <text>The chance that an invasion will depart during the current process_targets update. This is called every 1
            to 5 in-game minutes.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_base_priority_desc">
        <text>How much the faction prioritises bases.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_resource_priority_desc">
        <text>How much the faction prioritises resource points.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_flag_priority_desc">
        <text>How much a base prioritises points that are flagged for their owning faction in the
            gamedata/configs/misc/simulation_objects_props.ltx file. For instance if Clear Sky is looking at a territory
            point, it will increase the priority for a point by 2 if in that file the point has csky = 1 defined for it.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_is_being_targeted_priority_desc">
        <text>If a base is being targeted by another base, it will add this much priority to it in order to attempt to
            counter the invasion.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_target_weaker_priority_desc">
        <text>How much a base prioritises points which have less powerful squads present.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_target_stronger_priority_desc">
        <text>How much a base prioritises points which have more powerful squads present.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_target_on_same_level_priority_desc">
        <text>How much a base prioritises points which are on the same level as itself.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_max_smart_targets_per_base_desc">
        <text>The maximum possible number of targets a base can have at once. Bases will add extra targets beyond their
            minimum number of targets based on their faction aggression setting. Higher faction aggressions cause bases
            to add targets faster. This setting should be kept at or above the minimum smart targets per base.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_faction_min_smart_targets_per_base">
        <text>Minimum smart targets per base</text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_min_smart_targets_per_base_desc">
        <text>A base will always target at least this many locations. The base will send squads to empty targets, or
            invade hostile targets.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_resource_count_modifier_desc">
        <text>How many resource points are added to a faction's resource count. This can be negative. Higher numbers
            cause stronger squads to spawn.
        </text>
    </string>
    <string id="ui_mm_alife_warfare_stalker_base_count_modifier_desc">
        <text>How many bases are added to a faction's owned base count. This can be negative. Higher numbers cause
            longer base respawn times, approaching the value set by maximum respawn time.
        </text>
    </string>
</string_table>